Danish Irfan Shah bin Muzaffar Shah

No. 30, Jalan Pelangi 9, Taman Seri Pelangi, Banting +6012-363 1097

danishshah1712@gmail.com

Versatile software engineer works well both as part of the team and independently. Stay organized doing tasks to ensure a deliverable is on time and experience for both web and mobile app development. Experienced in doing several freelance works for small mobile apps and one for a cross-platform system.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Good Works Technology Sdn. Bhd.

SS15, Subang Jaya

Intern Software Engineering

Sep 2022 - Feb 2023

- Testing and verify every feature done by development team. Any bugs will be report and notify the developers.
- Construct an automation testing using Datadog for any basic features such as login/out, CRUD operations.
- Support consultant team to deliver workflow and user's guide for client.
- Leading the improvement of UI/UX design of old page in terms of usability and accessibility using Figma.

Raees Revolution Rekascape, Cyberjaya

Software Developer

Apr 2023 - Nov 2023

- Build ease-to-use UIUX design based on requirements that have been provided using Figma.
- Design database design for developers to refers and documentation.
- Create a smooth web application with many use cases and consideration of scenarios.
- Maintain the system by solving any issues reported and added any new features.
- Build a static web for marketing the software product.

EDUCATION

UiTM Dengkil, Selangor

Foundation of Engineering

Jun 2018 - Mar 2019

CGPA: 4.00

Universiti Kebangsaan Malaysia

Bangi, Selangor

Bachelor of Software Engineering in Development Information System

CGPA: 3.79

Sep 2019 - Sep 2023

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

Bengkel Komputeran Menggunakan Blockly

Dec 2020

Teaching local primary and secondary students' concepts about programming through the web app, Blockly.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Java, SQL, NoSQL, Laravel, VueJs
- Skilled in front-end using VueJs
- Familiar with combination of Laravel and Livewire to build a web application
- Experienced in building mobile apps using a pair of Java and Firebase
- Extensive experience with Agile Development
- Experienced in updating a server (shared hosting) using cPanel platform

CERTIFICATIONS

Responsive Web Design Jul 2021

Participating an introduction of responsive web design at freeCodeCamp.org.

JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

Oct 2021

Participating a JavaScript algorithm and data structures tutorial at freeCodeCamp.org.

PAST PROJECTS

PPSWE Nov 2021 – Jul 2022

• A pill tracker mobile apps used to help and alert elderly or any others patient to take prescription medicine.

UKMads Oct 2021 – Jan 2022

- A web app that able to help any business or organization by advertising their product or events.
- UKMads also displaying all the advertisement for the public.

MyData *Apr 2023 – Oct 2023*

- A web app that helps clinic staff to organize patient's record and data.
- It can generate a monthly report based on various type of report.

Nurse2U Asia Oct 2023 – Nov 2023

- A static website that promoting Nurse2U mobile apps.
- Nurse2U is a product that allows user to find a freelance nurse services.